Joseph Sciorra collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. Religious feasts and processions/Giglio Feast and other (primarily Italian American) religious feasts and processions, ca. 1903-2018
  - Subseries 1. Oversized materials related to Giglio feast and associated events, ca. 1984-2018
    - Brooklyn Giglio Boys Club, 4th Annual Columbus Day Giglio Party, October 12, 2017, AFC 2018/065: GR030; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - Coors Distributing Company of New York Presents the Feast of Our Lady of Mount Carmel & St. Paulinus of Nola (Brooklyn), July 7-July 18, 1993, AFC 2018/065: GR031; 1 poster (Folder OS05)
    - Il Giglio a New York: Storie di Emigrazione: La Transformazione della Festa da Nola a New York (in collaboration con John D. Calandra - Italian American Institute / Queens College), June 19-June 24, 2002, AFC 2018/065: GR032; 1 poster (Folder OS05)
    - Our Lady of Mt. Carmel & St. Paulinus Italian Street Feast (nightly entertainment & bazaar), July 2-19 (no year), AFC 2018/065: GR033; 1 poster (Folder OS05)
    - Take a Walk on the Northside! (shopping guide poster from Northside Merchants Association, the City of New York, and People's Firehouse Housing and Community Development Co.), undated, AFC 2018/065: GR034; 1 poster (Folder OS05)
- Series 2. Italian American religious expression and material culture, ca. 1974-2017
  Research, writing, fieldwork, and audiovisual documentation of a variety of religious altars and shrines.
  - Subseries 1. Shrines, domestic altars, and grottos, ca. 1981-2013
    - 9/11 Yard memorial, 2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Adriana Scalamandre Bitter fundraising memo, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Altars, Shrines, and Grottos Among Brooklyn's Italian American, article drafts, ca. 1982-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Altars, shrines, and grottos, 1/2, ca. 1983, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Altars, shrines, and grottos, 2/2, ca. 1983, 1 folder of manuscripts with 2 contact sheets, 9 photographic prints, black and white (3 are 3x5; 3 are 5x7; 2 are 8x10), 3 photographic prints, color (8x10) (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Altars, shrines, and grottos, negatives, ca. 1983, AFC 2018/065: PH119; 5 film negatives, color (120 mm); 8 film negatives, color (35mm); 56 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Altars/High art, 1984, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Alti stone-studded shrine, enfant Prague, July 9, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Alti stone-studded shrine, enfant Prague, July 9, 2005, AFC 2018/065: PH113; 12 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Angel's Circle 9/11 Memorial Garden, Staten Island, 2003-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Article about Lisanti family chapel in Voices magazine, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Article about Madonna Nera in Voices magazine, 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Articles about Christmas displays, 1984-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Articles about holiday displays in NYC, 1/2, 1983-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Articles about holiday displays in NYC, 2/2, 1983-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Bensonhurst RIP memorial wall art, 2005-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts with 18 photogaphic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Book proposal chapters, 2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Borderlines: Migrant Writing and Italian Identities, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Buddhist statue, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Building/landscaping aesthetics, 1983-1994, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Building restoration of sacred sites, 2000-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Built With Faith reviews, 2015-2017, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Canarsie, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts with 18 photo prints, color (4 x 6) (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Carroll Garden shrines, afc2018065_dc075; 3 photographs (TIF)
    - A ceremony celebrating Lisanti family chapel, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Ceremony to nominate OLMC Grotto to NY State List of Historic Places, 1/2, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts with 17 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Ceremony to nominate OLMC Grotto to NY State List of Historic Places, 2/2, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Chicago candle houses, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Chris DeVito, 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts with 29 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Chris DeVito, 2004, AFC 2018/065: PH114; 18 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Chris DeVito interview, 1989-1990, AFC 2018/065: PH099; 12 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 62)
    - Christmas Crib (Nesta de Robeck), 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Christmas displays - Joseph Di Martino, 1985-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (3.5x4 (polaroid)) (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Christmas displays - Mangione family, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Christmas displays - Pelham Parkway North, 1988-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Christmas displays - vandals, 1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Christmas house decoration paper, ca. 1987-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 12/19)
    - Christmas house display companies, 1999-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Christmas house displays, notes, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Christmas in pop culture, 2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Christmas lights - complaints from neighbors, 1992-2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Christmas lights slides, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH040; 14 slides, color (35 mm) (Box 53)
    - Christmas material culture articles, ca. 1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Christmas Putz, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 45/10)
    - Christmas store window displays, 1990-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Christmas traditions, 1987-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Crazy displays, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Cultural landscape syllabi and bibliographies, 1997-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/9)
    - CUNY Diversity Grant (Domestic Needlework), 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Danish television program on memorial art, 2004, afc2018065_dc008; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Decorating contests, 2004-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Documentaries, Dyker Lights, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Documentaries, Kings of Christmas, 2005-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Documentary, Kings of Christmas, 2005, afc2018065_dc062; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Documentaries, Outta Control Christmas (HGTV), 2005-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Dolce and Gabanna/Needlework fundraising, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Domestic Needlework conference, 1/2, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Domestic Needlework conference, 2/2, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Domestic Needlework symposium, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Domestic sacred space, ca. 1997-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Dyker Lights (documentary), 2001, AFC 2018/065: MV008; 1 videocassette
    - Elite landscapes, 1994-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Ex Voto exhibit, 2011-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Fieldwork and transcribed interviews on OLMC grottos, 1988-1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Francesco Pepe, 2009-2011, 1 folder of manuscripts with 52 photographic prints, color (4x5.5 inches) (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Fred Massimi fundraising memo, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Gardening/horticulture, 2003-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Gino Vitale, Red Hook, 2004-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Gods of the City: Religion and the American Urban Landscape (book), correspondence, ca. 1990-1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 45/13)
    - Grotto, 1979-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Grotto article by Sciorra, 1993, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Grotto material, ca. 1991-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Grotto newspaper accounts, 1987-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Grotto-Lisanti talk, ca. 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Grottos and shrines, Dickeyville, Wisconsin, ca. 1982, 1 folder of manuscripts with 38 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Grottos and shrines, Dickeyville, Wisconsin, ca. 1982, AFC 2018/065: PH125; 32 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Guarino/Frank Seddio, 2006-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts with 4 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Guarino/Frank Seddio, 2006-2012, AFC 2018/065: PH121; 4 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Hamburger, Inc. (supplier), 1989-1994, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Harlem research, New York Public Library, ca. 2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Harlem step altar, July 16, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts with 21 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Harlem step altar, July 16, 2005, AFC 2018/065: PH110; 14 film negatives, color (Box 63)
    - Harris Taormina, Anthony Di Biasi, 1985-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Harris Taormina, Anthony Di Biasi, 1985-2006, AFC 2018/065: PH121; 8 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Historic Preservation and the Italian American Presence in New York City (symposium), 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Italian American architects, 2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Italian American shrines, 1979-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts with 7 prints, color (4x6); 1 photographic print, black and white (5x7) (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Italian American statue makers, 1989-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Italian Ex Votos, ca. 1974-1999, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Italian war prisoners altar, 2002-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Italian yard shrines in media, ca. 1988-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/6)
    - James Quitoni, 1/2, ca. 1991-2015, 1 folder of manuscripts with 22 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 15/7)
    - James Quitoni, 2/2, ca. 1991-2015, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (4x6) (Box-folder 15/8)
    - James Quitoni, 2/2, ca. 1991-2015, AFC 2018/065: PH115; 14 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
    - James Quitoni, St. Anthony, 1989-2016, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Jersey yard shrine, 1992-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Joe Caria Pierlucca, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/11)
    - John D. Calandra Italian American Institute events, 2012-2018, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Joseph Pezza, 2002-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts with 19 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Joseph Pezza, 2002-2007, AFC 2018/065: PH116; 26 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Joseph Pezza, Padre Pio petitions, 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Joseph Vitolo, ca. 1987-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts with 13 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Joseph Vitolo, ca. 1987-2007, AFC 2018/065: PH112; 12 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
    - Julio Dones, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Kitsch/neighborhood description, 1997-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Landmarking, 2003-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Landmarks Project, G. Meyers, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Landscapers, 2001-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Laura Hansen - Rosebank Grotto, 1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Laura Savini, WLIW fundraising memo, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Lawns and statues, 1/2, 1962-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 46/2)
    - Lawns and statues, 2/2, 1962-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 46/3)
    - Lisanti Chapel building documents, ca. 1981-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Lisanti Chapel ceremony, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Lisanti Chapel follow up, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Lisanti Chapel nomination for State Register of Historic Places, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Lisanti documents, 1974-2004, AFC 2018/065: PH053; 11 slides, color (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Lisanti documents, 1/2, 1974-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Lisanti ViewMasters, afc2018065_dc070; 24 photographs (TIF)
    - Lisanti documents, 2/2, 1974-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts with 47 photographic prints, color (44 are 4x6, 3 are 4.5x4.5) (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Lisanti documents, 2/2, 1974-2004, AFC 2018/065: PH131; 44 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Lisanti family article, and Black Madonna article in Voices, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Lisanti family memoir, ca. 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Lisanti family tree, 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Lisanti slides, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH054; 10 slides, color (35mm) (Box 54)
    - MA Thesis: Italian Americans in Rosebank, Staten Island (Diana E. Thompson), 1972, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 16/17)
    - Madonna del Carmine, Madonna del Pettoruto, ca. 2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Memorial shrine to Tommy, Bergen Beach, July 9, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts with 11 photogaphic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Memorial shrine to Tommy, Bergen Beach, July 9, 2005, AFC 2018/065: PH117; 8 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Misc. Ex Voto, votive offerings, ca. 2011, 1 folder of manuscripts with 3 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Miscellaneous materials: shrines and Feast of the Giglio, ca. 2016-2018, 1 folder of manuscripts with 3 photographic prints (2 are 5x7, 1 is 3.5x5) (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Beccaio, Festa dei Gigli di Nola, 2014, afc2018065_dc071; 7 audio files (WAV)
    - Mt. Carmel Society/Grotto documents, 1984-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 contact sheet, black and white; 3 photographic prints (1 color 4x5; 2 black and white 4x5) (Box-folder 46/8)
    - Mt. Carmel Society/Grotto documents, 1984-2005, AFC 2018/065: PH126; 34 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Needlework conference confirmation, memos, addresses, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Notes on new Rosebank essay, 1989-1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Nunzio D'Alto, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 17/7)
    - OLMC Grotto - certificate, State Register of Historic Places, 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/8)
    - OLMC Grotto nomination for National Register of Historic Places, 1/2, ca. 1989-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/9)
    - OLMC Grotto nomination for National Register of Historic Places, 2/2, ca. 1989-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/10)
    - OLMC Grotto slides (by Lillian Caruana), undated, AFC 2018/065: PH046; 16 slides, color (35mm) (Box 54)
    - Our Lady of Mount Carmel Devotion in Brooklyn, 1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Perspectives in Vernacular Architecture article, 1986-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Peter and Janet Marcolini, 1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Puerto Rican East Harlem OLMC Altar, July 16, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts with 3 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Puerto Rican East Harlem OLMC Altar, July 16, 2005, AFC 2018/065: PH118; 7 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Puerto Rican East Harlem OLMC Altar, July 16, 2005, AFC 2018/065: PH036; 1 slide, color (35mm) (Box 51)
    - Queens College Internal Approvals, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Queens College/Factories, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Readers Reports for "Built With Faith," ca. 2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Religious banners exhibit, 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Returning Home, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Roadside memorials, 1999-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Rosebank, Staten Island, 1988-2017, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/1)
    - S. Gandolfo storefront chapel, ca. 1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Saint Donato sidewalk altar, Francestca Mazza, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Saints/virgins, miracles, and apparitions, 1987-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Shrine correspondence, ca. 1984-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Shrine field research (Bart A. Roselli, Martha Cooper), 1985, AFC 2018/065: PH037; 6 slides, color (35mm) (Box 51)
    - Shrine field research, 1/2, 1983-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints, color (3 are 3.5x5; 4 are 4x6; 1 is 5x7) (Box-folder 46/4)
    - Shrine field research, 2/2, 1983-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 46/5)
    - Shrine grant applications, 1984-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Shrine magazines/articles, 1984-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Shrine newspaper articles, 1984-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Shrine notes and photos, ca. 1984-1985, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints, color (7 are 4x6, 1 is 5x6) (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Shrine notes and photos, ca. 1984-1985, AFC 2018/065: PH120; 88 film negatives, color (35mm); 2 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 64)
    - Shrine production grant, 1986-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Shrine research, 1/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts with 3 photographic prints, black and white (3.5x5) (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Shrine research, 2/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Shrine show script, ca. 1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Shrine slide show drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Shrine slide show, #1, Institute for Italian American Studies, Inc., undated, AFC 2018/065: PH063; 111 slides, color (35mm) (Box 56-57)
    - Shrine slide show, #2, Institute for Italian American Studies, Inc., undated, AFC 2018/065: PH064; 70 slides, color (35mm) (Box 57)
    - Shrine slides, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH038; 287 slides, color (35mm) (Box 51-53)
    - Shrine talks, 1988-1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Shrine, 215th St., Bronx, 2000-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts with 10 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Shrine, 215th St., Bronx, 2000-2001, AFC 2018/065: PH130; 5 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 65)
    - Shrines, 2006-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Shrines article - Penfield Press, 1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Shrines/material culture: Ikey images, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH067; 21 slides, color (35mm) (Box 58)
    - Shrines/material culture: Lisanti Chapel article for Voices Magazine, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Somerville (Cambridge, MA) illuminations, 2001-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Illuminations book draft 2006, afc2018065_dc063; 13 document files (DOC), 38 photographs (JPG, PSD)
    - St. Francis Grotto, Williamsburg, 1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/9)
    - St. Francis of Paola Church, 1993, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/10)
    - St. Joseph Church, Rosebank, Staten Island, 2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/11)
    - St. Lucy Grotto, Bronx, 1992-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/12)
    - St. Philip Neri, 1998-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/13)
    - St. Rocco's and Stephen La Rocca, 2009-2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/14)
    - St. Rocco's Statue - Life Magazine, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Studies of front yard devotions, 2001-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Swedish television program about memorial art, 2004, afc2018065_dc007; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - The Nativity Scene (book), ca. 1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Underground gardens, ca. 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Embodied Placemaking, 2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 19/19)
    - USA yard shrines, others, 1/2, ca. 1972-1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/1)
    - USA yard shrines, others, 2/2, ca. 1972-1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Votive displays, Walker Evans, ca. 2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Williamsburg notes for Built With Faith (book), 2004-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Writings about yard shrines, 1/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Writings about yard shrines, 2/2, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Yard shrine articles by Sciorra, 1989-1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Yard shrines as identifiers re. neighborhoods, ca. 1985-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Yard shrine bibliography, ca. 1984, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Yard shrines Bensonhurst/Gravesend, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts with 23 photographic prints, color (4x6); 3 photographic prints, color (5x7) (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Yard shrines Bensonhurst/Gravesend, 2005, AFC 2018/065: PH111; 11 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)
    - "Yard Shrines of Italian New York" article in Culturefront magazine, 1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Yard shrines Williamsburg, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts with 6 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Yard shrines, Anthony and Theresa Prisco, 1982, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Yard shrines, Furri and Louise Oliva, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Yard shrines/altars papers and research, 1988-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 20/15)
    - Yard shrines: Robert Iovino interview transcripts, 1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Sub-subseries 1: Black Madonna (Madonna Nera), ca. 1989-2006
      Research and documentation of Black Madonna, a Catholic depiction of the Virgin Mary, usually in the form of statues or paintings.
      - Black Madonna article and event, 2003-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/2)
      - Black Madonna articles, 1993-1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/3)
      - Black Madonna events and exhibit, 2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/4)
      - Black Madonna exhibit, 2003-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 21/5)
      - Black Madonna exhibit artifacts, ca. 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts with 25 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 21/6)
      - Black Madonna exhibit artifacts, ca. 2002-2003, AFC 2018/065: PH104; 8 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 63)